

Contacts

+380-093-594-1984

sirov@ukr.net

Telegram

GitHub

Linkedin

Nosivka, Ukraine

Tech Skills

- HTML5
- CSS
- PHP
- MySQL
- JavaScript
- SASS
- TypeScript
- React
- Redux
- Node.js
- Laravel
- Mongo.DB
- Netlify
- Render.com

Soft Skills

- · Critical thinking
- Time management
- Problem-solving
- Communication
- Creativity

Languages

- Ukrainian native
- Russian upper-intermediate
- English upper-intermediate

Oleh Syrovatko Junior Full Stack developer

Summary

With over 10 years of experience as a full-stack developer, including working on a large-scale social ped project, I am excited to pursue a role as a Junior Front-End Developer. I have successfully contributed to the creation of a popular social network for Ukrainian settlements, which attracted 583K unique visitors last year. I am confident that my skills, passion and experience in building user-centric applications will enable me to make valuable contributions to your company.

Project Experience

<u>lua.com.ua</u> (HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, MySQL, Laravel)

First social network about all Ukrainian settlements. Contain more than 1 million photos and 115k users organized by Laravel Framework. Role: Team lead. Individual project.

afc.cn.ua, GitHub (HTML, SAAS, CSS, JS, PHP, MySQL)

It's a little project about some building company. Several pages introduse products, projects, feedback, contacts and admin panel. Role: Team lead. Individual project.

MIMIHO, GitHub (HTML, SASS, JS, Parce)

It's a small project about restaurant. All the pages mobile adapted, have excelent performance, accessibility.

Role: Team lead. Group project.

Movies, GitHub Front GitHub Back (TypeScript React Node.js MongoDB)

A movie site, connected to a backend API. Users can register, log in, view, search, add, and remove favorite movies, and manage bookmarks. Role: Developer. Individual project

Work Experience

Chief Accountant

PF Sa-Ha Trans 2016-2024

- Accounting: Financial record-keeping and compliance
- International Logistics: Managing global shipments and deliveries
- Finance: Financial operations oversight and analysis

Achieving an increase in the company's profitability and an increase in its capital more than 30%.

Full Stack Developer

First allukrainian social network 2006-present

- full development lifecycle, including concept-to-deployment
- ensuring best practices and quality standards
- conducting code reviews, provide code quality and maintainability
- implementing scalable database structures
- handling large volumes of photos and user data

Achievement: 583K unique visitors per last year.

Education

2022 - 2023IT School GoIT, Fullstack Developer

2000 - 2005Kyiv National Economic University, Master of accounting,

analysis and auditing